[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What medical term refers to hair loss?", "correct_answer": "Alopecia", "incorrect_answers": ["Alocasia", "Preeclampsia", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was the first person nominated for the Oscar for Producer (Best Picture), Director, Actor and Screenwriter for the same movie.", "correct_answer": "Orson Welles", "incorrect_answers": ["John Huston", "Otto Preminger", "William Wyler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does to blave mean according to the movie The Princess Bride?", "correct_answer": "To bluff", "incorrect_answers": ["To raise", "To cheat", "To fold"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of milk is Brussels cheese made of?", "correct_answer": "Cows milk", "incorrect_answers": ["Buffalo milk", "Sheeps milk", "Goats milk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The slogan Sub Umbra Floreo, or Under the Shade I Flourish is the national motto of what Central American country?", "correct_answer": "Belize", "incorrect_answers": ["Costa Rica", "Guatemala", "Nicaragua"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Ocelot is a nocturnal cat that is also called by this name in certain regions.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["McKenneys Wildcat", "Jaguarete", "Painted Leopard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What invention is credited to American Melville R. Bissell?", "correct_answer": "The carpet sweeper", "incorrect_answers": ["Indoor carpeting", "The integrated circuit", "The vacuum cleaner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This component produces adenosinetriphosphate, which increases the cells vitality and enables the body to release quick burst of energy.", "correct_answer": "Creatine", "incorrect_answers": ["Estrogen", "Glutamine", "Adrenaline"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mars moon Deimos orbits the closest to its planet of any moon in the Solar System.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the main terrorist played by Alan Rickman in Die Hard?", "correct_answer": "Hans Gruber", "incorrect_answers": ["Karl Evans", "Jorge Schuman", "James Lolskan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who takes over as Don in The Godfather Part II, when Michael leaves after an attempt on his life?", "correct_answer": "Tom Hagen", "incorrect_answers": ["Frank Pentangeli", "Al Neri", "Fredo Corleone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the villains mistress in The Man with the Golden Gun, who gets killed for having betrayed her lover to James Bond?", "correct_answer": "Andrea Anders", "incorrect_answers": ["Louisette  Doumergue", "Vivian  Ratopek", "Gisela  Mohnfeld"]}]